

Raul Ignacio Ereño

Full Stack Developer

Argentina

PROFILE

I am a Full Stack developer with experience in both personal and team projects. I am passionate about web development and its entire ecosystem. I specialize in the MERN and PERN technology stacks (MongoDB/PostgreSQL, Express, React, and NodeJS) and I am constantly learning new technologies to have a broad view of the industry. I am an empathetic person who enjoys helping my colleagues to achieve the objectives of a project.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Renten, Henry(professional practice)

10/2022 - 12/2022

My role in this project was as a Full Stack Developer. I was responsible, along with a colleague, for building the REST API. Later on, I worked with the frontend developers to complete the web app's layout. We followed the Agile Scrum methodology, which included delivery deadlines, daily meetings, user stories, sprints, and other good practices of this framework.

Stack: Typescript - Angular - NodeJs - Express - PostgreSQL

NGRX - MaterialUI - Cloudinary - MercadoPago

https://rent-ten.vercel.app/home

Teaching Assistant Tutor, Henry

09/2022 - 12/2022

Full-Stack Teaching Assistant Bootcamp Assistant (TA) for Full-Stack Development Students. Main tasks:

- Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration to the study group.
- Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- Propose ideas to improve the Bootcamp processes.

SPA Dogs Breeds, Henry(professional practice)

09/2022 - 12/2022

Creation of a website consuming an API with information about dog breeds. Individually implemented HTML, React with Javascript, using Sass for styling, and on the backend implemented Node.js, Express, Sequelize and PostgreSQL as the database.

https://pi-dogs-henry.netlify.app/

SpeakEasy, NoCountry(professional practice)

02/2023 - 03/2023

Although my profile is focused on web development, I am not afraid to take on challenges, such as the NoCountry practices that connect you with an interdisciplinary team to improve soft skills and teamwork through the Scrum methodology. On this occasion, I was responsible for creating some views with Dart and Flutter, the latter being a mobile development framework. Additionally, I helped my teammates connect all the views with the Firebase database used.

Stack: Flutter, Dart and Firebase.

https://github.com/raulereno/speak-easy

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer (PERN Stack), Henry

07/2022 - 12/2022

Over 1000 hours of coding, making me a standout developer in:

- JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- Node.js, Express.js
- Sequelize, PostgreSQL
- React, Redux

Technologies learned on my own for the completion of the final assignment:

- TypeScript
- Angular 14
- NgRx
- MaterialUI, Cloudinary, MercadoPago and Auth0

Full Stack Developer(MERN Stack), CoderHouse

2022 - presente

A set of courses that total over 500 hours of coding and include multiple weekly challenges along with final projects, where throughout this certification, we learn MongoDB, Express, React, and Node.js. Among these courses are some such as Web Development, JavaScript, and ReactJS that award you the Frontend Developer certificate. Currently, I am taking the last course, which is Backend Development.

Final project of ReactJS:

https://github.com/raulereno/cursoReact-desafios

Initial Java Developer, National Technological University

02/2023 - presente

CS50's Web Programming with Python and Javascript,

12/2022 - presente

Harvard University

LANGUAGES

Spanish	• • • •	English	• • • • •
Native		B2- Upper Intermediate	

SKILLS

JavaScript | React | TypeScript | Angular | NodeJs | Express | MongoDB | PostgreSQL Git/Github | Trello | Slack | Agile Scrum | Jira